vacationrentals411.com 2008-10-18

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy** **  
Please Read Carefully**  

**Your Personal Information**

Your personal information is not shared with third parties, . 

**Information We Gather**

At various times you may contribute your personal data to us. For example, in order to process a request or enquiry you may make concerning a property or transaction, we need to know all or some of the following: your full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of a member's (advertising) listing, a method of payment. You may also contribute personal data to us at other times, such as when registering on the Site. 

**Newsletters**

As a member of the Site, you will receive our "Owner"" newsletter, which is an integral part of the service we provide. Users may cancel their subscription to these newsletters at any time. 

**Inquiries**

Site users may send inquiries to members via click able links on Site listings. If you choose to send an inquiry through these links, your personal information, including your e-mail address and any other information you supply, will be visible to the member in question so that they might reply directly to you. If you call the member, you may be asked to leave a return telephone number. Do not share information in the e-mail or phone call that you are not prepared to allow them to have, including, but not limited to, credit card and bank account information. These inquiries are both sent to the individual member you selected and retained by us. The resulting inquiry is available for review only by the member to whom they were initially addressed and to our customer service employees, who may be asked by members for their past inquiry information. While the content of these inquiries is not shared with any other party, the Site may, from time to time, use third party e-mail servers to send and track receipt of the inquiry e-mails, and analyze the pattern of inquiry usage reported by these third party tracking systems; [the resulting information is used and stored only in an anonyms form. 

**How Do We Protect Your Personal Information Once We Have It?**

We take appropriate measures to guard against unauthorized or unlawful processing of your personal data and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your personal data. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We have security measures in place to protect our user database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each user's responsibility: All personal information is stored on a secure server. We do not store credit card numbers or related identifying information on any Site server. All such information is stored by our credit card processing partner, on their secured servers, and is protected via its proprietary methods. Please remember that many services and transactions are performed by our business partners. Our privacy policy and our security or common practices do not apply to other companies. What is a Cookie and Why Do We Use Them? A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store in a Web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. We may use cookies to store some personal preferences for your future visits. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly; therefore, your time spent on our site can be more personalized and productive. You'll find that cookies are an industry standard and are used at most major Web sites in much the same way we use them here at our Site. If you wish, you can prevent cookie files from using (non-personal) information about you by either deleting the cookie folder in your browser or by putting your browser's Privacy setting higher, but doing so will mean that (a) your use of the Site will be adversely affected (and quite possibly entirely prevented), (b) your experience of this and other sites that use cookies to enhance or personalize your experience will be adversely affected, and (c) you will not be presented with advertising that reflects the way that you use our, and other, sites. You find out how to make these changes to your browser at this site: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies>. 

**How do I correct or update my information?**

We allow our users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods: 

  * E-mail the request to vacationrentals411.com 

  * Mail the request to us at 9001 Canoga, Canoga Park, California 91304. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and post the new version on the Site. When we do so, we will notify you of the fact on the main screen of the Site and the new version of this Privacy Policy will take effect, and will govern all Site services and your relationship with us: 

**How Long Will We Keep Your Personal Data?**

We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which you consent under the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it. 

**Disclosure for Legal Reasons**

Your personal data may be disclosed if we or an entity processing your data on our behalf are compelled to do so by law, or receive a valid, legally compliant request by a law enforcement or governmental authority. 

**How do I contact you?**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, we encourage you to contact us .
